Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
With Asta's help, Fuegolion subdued the insane mage who had let loose an undead army upon the capital in his search for revenge.
I get that you wanted people to take you seriously, but I don't understand why you had to do it like this.
Magic?
Allow me to thank you for your service, Magic Knights.
What the...
Caught off guard by a spatial magic spell, the elite members of the Magic Knights were pulled from the attack's aftermath and transported far from the capital.
I knew there was a strong spatial magic user working with them, but even so...
To do this, transporting us all would require great skill.
Spatial magic again, eh?
Very well. Maybe now we'll get to the bottom of this.
Fuegolion Vermillion, captain of the Crimson Lion Kings, was himself warped away to a mysterious realm.
It's you!
Meanwhile, having avoided the spatial ambush that ensnared his colleagues, Yuno battled a powerful witch who used her Ash curse magic to leave him in a state of total sensory deprivation.
But then...
I'm not done!
There's just one very important thing to know about me.
The truth is...
I would rather give my life than lose!
Win spirit magic!
Silk scratch!
boşver!
Yes ho!
Maybe
What's wrong with all Rose?
Let's just rest him
Why?
Support me
Stop
ifornia
I'm all over.
My shell.
Shell!
Wonderful!
Yes!
This little shortcake knows how to eat.
It's a chef's trade come true!
Keep going.
Savor every last bite.
Yes, eat it all!
The entire capital's under siege,
and this is what they care about?
You just say when you're ready for more,
and I'll make you seconds, even thirds!
Hooray!
What now?
A witch?
We're under attack!
What the hell do you think we've been trying to tell you?
Please, chef!
It's time to bail!
Run for it, shortcake!
My mana!
It's draining!
I need to steal some more!
What are you doing, shortcake?
Just run!
That little girl, saturated with mana!
She's greasy with the stuff!
I need every last drop of it!
Give it to me!
I want it!
If you would!
Wait, you don't mean...
Not my lunch!
No way, lady!
Now give it to me!
I need mana!
I can still sense her mana.
That witch has to be alive somewhere.
I won't last much longer.
What?
That's a massive surge of magic!
Relinquish it to me!
I told you no.
And when I say no, I mean no.
I mean no.
This is ridiculous!
You won't think so for long.
Cotton creation magic!
Strike of the sleeping sheep!
That was awesome!
Well, you see that?
My cooking gave the little shortcake's magic power
the boost it needed to defeat the witch!
Seriously?
Chef, sir?
I'll work with you for as long as I live!
You saved us with your feast!
It was nothing.
I don't care who you are.
Nobody ever lays a hand on my food.
Your patronage is not wanted here!
What?
Please tell me I'm beautiful.
My dear Eliza.
Yes?
I'll always love you.
Young or old.
And I love you.
Eliza!
My dearest!
Young Meg!
Ha!
Wag!
Amelia!
Her.
My dearest!
Hi!
A child?
That outrageously powerful burst of magic.
Was that her?
She's wearing a black bull's robe.
It must have been.
You saved my boy!
Oh, uh, here.
I don't get it, but sure.
Thank you so...
My princely thank you, sustenance!
Um, I owe you a tremendous debt, noble sir.
Could you tell me what...
A short wig?
Oh, yeah, they're great!
You can try one if you want to.
Wait, no, no, no, no.
That's not it.
I'm...
Min...
Could you tell me what your name is?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
You can have one, but I know what a short wig is.
Here comes the crash.
I mean, I know about all sorts of meat.
That magic took a serious toll on my body.
It used up a ton of mana.
I need practice.
Gotta learn to be more efficient.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Look out!
Saved you!
Aah!
I guess I'll just need this to be on the way.
What is that infernal racket out there?
Will you order them to quiet down?
Don't they know it's my nap time?
I'll look into it, sire.
Is it him?
It's about time he made his return.
You forever want a place in our hearts, little shortcake.
Just stop on by whenever you're hungry, day or night.
We'll feed you until you're ready to pop.
Yay!
You evil bastard!
Tell me where you sent my brother!
He's just toying with you.
He wasn't the one who cast this spatial magic spell.
But the pinpoint accuracy of it.
No one could pull that off unless they were close to their target.
They're hiding nearby.
Asta?
He was hiding beneath the pile of corpses?
Nice observation skills.
I had a feeling you'd suss out my magical transformations.
But I couldn't even get past you with a shabby putrescent disguise.
You really are quite the animal.
Hmm.
Regardless, it's already over now.
Over?
What is?
APS
Ha-ha.
AHHHHHHHHHHH!
OHH!!!
NOOOOO!!!
귀 celto!!
Fya'd..
But how...?
How can someone be that strong? That's just... insane!
They... his arm...
This can't be... No...
You can't die... Fuegoleon... No... Not my brother... He would never lose... He'd never lose... NEVER!
It's Captain Fuegoleon's grimoire! Wait, if his grimoire's still intact then... He's not dead yet! We have to stop the bleeding!
Impossible... There's no way... If only Mimosa were here, she could fix this...
Leopold! Your brother's grimoire is starting to disintegrate! Snap out of it! I need your help!
My brother...
Leopold! Are you just going to let your brother die?
Well, Magic Knight, not so sure of yourself anymore now, are you?
Pull it together!
He still has a reserve of magic power!
Ah!
Perhaps you could have become a great man if you had gone down a different path. This is where the lack of a just heart has led you.
I lack a just heart, do I? Well, I have to tell you, the way I live my life, my heart's done just right by me!
Looks like you'll have to save your preaching for the afterlife, Captain!
You've fulfilled your purpose here.
Huh?
Take your leave, Radies, before the other knights arrive.
No way! Not yet!
Huh?
It's little Oster, right? Don't worry, I promise to kill you soon enough! And make a plaything of your corpse! Something we can both look forward to, you brat!
Ah!
Yeah!
Asta!
I'm not close enough. I'll never make it!
Just let him go!
He's losing too much blood! He has to stop!
I can do this!
Remember what Captain Foigolion told you? Stay calm and think!
There must be some way I can stop him! I just have to figure out what it is!
Spatial magic is still magic! And I've still got my sword!
I'm gonna hack that spell to pieces!
What the hell?
The hell?
That hurts! You're gonna pay for that, you little wretch!
Unfortunate.
You're whining about a little cut after the pain you've caused!
You want pain? I'll give you pain!
You torture innocent people and laugh the whole time!
Stop it!
Those poor innocents you're so worried about? That only proves how weak they are!
It's just the natural order! The weaker mage will always succumb to the one with greater power!
And you... you were born to die, you magic-efficient swine!
The natural order, huh?
Then what do you call this?
That's right.
Maybe I don't have any magic, but I'm still the strongest one here!
And I'll prove it to everyone when I become the Wizard King!
Hey, Voltos! I could use a little help here!
Hmph. I've already done everything I can.
Anti-magic. It's trickier than I expected.
Seems like the smartest plan of action is to take care of him first.
He's gathering magic power. But for what?
Is he going to attack through a spatial portal?
Asta! Behind you!
Too late.
Being upset won't help us.
Always remember to stay calm. Right, brother?
Let's go, Asta!
Please be careful!
So what should I do?
I can't afford to lose Radies just yet.
Get away from me!
Stay back!
Get away, dammit!
How pitiful.
I come here after receiving word from the Master.
Only to arrive and find you fighting this pitiful indeed.
Indeed.
This magic. I've never felt anything so piercingly cold.
So now there's five of them?
This curse I've got on me.
None of these scrapes and scratches will stop bleeding.
I'm going to be in serious trouble if I lose any more blood.
I don't remember putting out the call for any extra help!
Really? You might want to try thanking us.
You know what would have happened to you if we hadn't shown up to bail you out?
You would have been captured, cut open, gutted, and skinned alive.
And if you are going to get dissected, I want to be the one to do it.
Will you shut up?
Well now, it looks like the tables have finally churned, you little brats!
Huh?
Hosta!
What was that?
Small surgery!
Now I'm ready to fight again!
Watch! I'll prove it to you!
Seriously?
Did he just strike himself with his own blades to dispel the curse?
Unbelievable!
Who would do that?
This kid's funny!
Can I pretty please dissect him later?
Be quiet and focus.
Lily, you're no fun.
Here's the thing.
I've been fighting an uphill battle since I was born.
No matter how many guys you've got,
and no matter what you do to me,
I'll cut right through every last one of you!
You hear me?!
Let's see what you've got!
Watch!
Hey, baby!
This is lots of how you're involved with your imagination.
Why does that change?
You see all these people in the world,
you see all the kinds of dark experiences,
and you, you know,
you see the染 indigenous through that session,
you see the termuseum.
And you see that you're repairing,
and you see that you must curl up.
And you need a snake.
Now, when rules, don't try them.
Yeah, while you don't expect,
you will react.
I hasn't started spots before you leave it in,
cause I'm sculpture- Sekitar,
大丈夫,
早々!
Thank you.
They'll never find me.
He's just toying with you.
He wasn't the one who cast this spatial magic spell.
But the pinpoint accuracy of it.
No one could pull that off unless they were close to their target.
They're hiding nearby.
They're never gonna find me.
He's not in here!
Not here!
You're dead.
Not here either!
Any second now, I'll make my grand entrance and blow the simple mines.
Well, we know he's not here, so let's check over that way.
Good thinking.
I'll bet you a month's wages that I'll find him before you do.
Wait, what?
Should I just lie here?
Hey, Magic Knights!
Fill up on my cooking and then do your fighting!
I'll fight on my own battlefield, the Kitchen!
Black Clover, page 26, Wounded Beasts!
My magic is cooking incredible food!